Juice-Juice
Seino, this is Juice-Juice.
We, Juice-Juice, have decided to release a new single.
It will be released on July 12.
Fly! The Bride is a song about the complicated feelings of a girl.
With lyrics that depict pain, hardship, and emotions,
The dance is rather intense, so I hope you enjoy the dance as well.
I hope you enjoy the dance as well. We are currently shooting a music video for Pride Pride.
Yay!
So we are dancing a lot,
How about you, Entoo-chan? Yes, I am. The dance is completely different from the previous new songs, and it is very intense,
I'm really looking forward to it.
Yes, I'm really looking forward to it.
Everyone is so cool, so please look forward to seeing what kind of work it will be.
Juice-Juice 10th Anniversary Concert Tour Juice!Juice at BUDOKAN on May 29,
Juice! Juice at BUDOKAN on May 29th, we will perform our new song "Pride Bright" for the first time.
I am very happy.
How do you like it, Mr. Ishikawa?
Yes, I am. I am very happy to perform the new song for the first time,
I would like to make the BUDOKAN concert a wonderful one,
I would be very happy if you could come to the show.
Thank you very much. I hope you will come to the show. Thank you very much.
That's all for Juice-Juice.
Hello! Stay, this time with Shori Nishida of BEYOOOOONDS' Chica Tetsu and Miyo Hirai of BEYOOOOONDS' Seasonings.
These two will be presenting this time, so please stay with us until the end.
Now that Golden Week is over, I am sure many of you are back to your normal mode.
We had a lot of work and tours during the Golden Week holidays, but what would you like to do if you had a holiday weekend?
If you had a consecutive holiday, what would you like to do?
Well, recently we have been talking about going on a trip together, and we were wondering where we would like to go.
We are from Kyoto, so it's not easy to say we want to go sightseeing in Kyoto.
We haven't really been to Kyoto because we're both from Kyoto.
If there is such an opportunity, I would like to go there.
I hope we can go there together more and more.
BEYOOOOONDS will be performing with an orchestra at the Tokyo Metropolitan Art Space Concert Hall on May 2nd.
BEYOOOOONDS had a biophonic performance with an orchestra at the Tokyo Metropolitan Art Space Concert Hall on May 2!
Yay!
Yes, yes!
But, you see, this recording is taking place right before the biophonic concert.
That's right.
I can't tell you how I feel about it yet, but...
The other day, we had a rehearsal for the biophonic concert and choreographed a new song that will be performed for the first time at the biophonic concert.
I can't stop being excited about it. I really like the new song.
I really like the new song, too. I think it's sparkling and fits the Beyoncé worldview, and I hope many people will listen to it.
I hope many people will listen to it. The choreography is full of highlights, so I hope people will pay attention to that too,
I hope many people will listen to it. Thank you very much.
Next week, on Monday, May 15, BEYOOOOONDS will be holding her concert tour NEOBIO at Budokan!
Wow!
Wow! Finally!
Soon, though.
I'm so nervous!
I'm so nervous.
But I'm really feeling the joy of being on stage with the 12 of us from our regular concerts.
I'm sure it will be even more special when we stand in the Budokan again.
I'm sure we'll all do our best.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Let's start with this video.
Please take a look.
Today, the trainees will show the results of their daily lessons in their solo performances. This diagnostic test is often a chance for them to make their debut.
It is such an important event, so let me introduce the trainees who will be taking this diagnostic test. Hinoha Yoshida
Kawashima Mifu Yoshida Hinoha Kawashima 3 min.
Oto o hana
How to get to Shimoitaita
Rena Kamimura
And here are the trainees who have joined us from this year's diagnostic test.
Makino Towa
Nina Hayashi
We are pleased to present you with the above members.
I look forward to working with you all.
Now, let me introduce today's panel of judges.
I would like to introduce today's judge, Ms. Maki Mitsuhashi, who has been instructing the trainees on their dance performance.
Maki Maki, please.
Next, we have Ms. Mariko Ueno, who is teaching the trainees how to sing.
Please give us a hand. Please welcome our singing instructor, Ms. Mariko Ueno.
Next, our first judge, who has provided numerous songs for the Hello Project group.
The writer Sho Hoshimei.
Thank you very much.
And then we have Lisa, the large type.
And another guest judge, Ms. Yoshikazu Miyamoto.
Yes, please!
These are the judges.
Now, everyone, please take your seats in the jury.So, ladies and gentlemen, please take your seats on the jury.
Yes, please. Now, it is getting glamorous.
First, we will start with the performance of the assigned song.
Let's start with the first performer. Please go ahead.
This is the one. Please, I want to love you for the rest of my life.
Thank you very much.
Not like this.
It's just mind adrenaline.
I can't live my life cheating.
No. No. No.
No.
Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Me
Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Me high tension this dunben I'm adrenaline
High tension
I've got it right
I can't cry, I can't cry, I can't cry, I can't cry
I can't cry, I can't cry, I can't cry
No tears, no tears, no tears
In a movie that's been the talk of the town
People didn't shake their heads at the rules
I can't say that the world is strange, my heart is thirsty and I'm told
Chasing and go for it
Baby baby baby show me love
Baby baby baby, show me love
Baby baby baby, show me loveBaby baby, show me love
I'm a little younger than you, but I know what it's like
Don't compare me to those stupid women.
Don't compare me to no woman
Oh Sweet Sweet Sweet
Best time tonight
Watch my heart twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle
Tonight's mission is a breeze
Mostly a success check
I'd do anything for you
You're the only one who knows what I want to do
You're the only one who knows.
I won't miss you.
I won't miss you. I won't miss you. I won't miss you.
No, I won't.
I'm not gonna miss you like this.
I'm here to pick you up like before
Don't break me like this Stop by me My heart can't take it anymore My first love is my last love
And I want to love you for the rest of my life
I want to love you forever
I can't go on like this
I want to love you for the rest of my life
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I'm adrenaline free
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you free
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
High tension.
Do it right
Thank you.
You're doing great, you're cool.
This is Shiori Nishida from BEYOOOOONDS' Chica Tetsu and Miyo Hirai from BEYOOOOONDS' Seasonings, and we're here at Halo! I'm going to ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and just answer at a quick pace.
The temperature is getting warmer and warmer, but what is your personal favorite item to coordinate for this season?
What is your new favorite thing right now?
Video Editing What is the workout that Mio Hirai is focusing on right now?
What do you think you have grown recently?
Power Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year Which song would Mio Hirai like to dance on stage at least once? 7 korobi yataki 7 korobi yataki oo by Angeleum! Yes, thank you!
He wants to do Angulum's 7 korobi yataki.
Looks like a good fit.
The members who dance and the members who sing are separated.
I thought it was very rare to have such a format, and I saw a video of Hikako Sasaki dancing by herself on Youtube, and it was so cool that I wanted to dance someday.
I think it's wonderful and I'd like to see it someday, so please do your best.
I'm not sure if it's because of the Japanese, but I think it's because of the NeoBio concert.
I don't know if you have Japanese, but there is a part in the concert called "Neovio" where I do the mc.
I was always saying "ah-ha-hi", but after the third or fourth time, I started to be able to mc a little more calmly, and I thought that was the latest growth.
It was really difficult for me to sing and speak in a normal way because I had been dancing and doing my best up to that point.
But you did a great job.
Thank you very much.
I think I am growing.
Questions for Shiori Nishida will be asked after the VTR.
Hallo! BEYOOOOONDS new single "Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler" Now on sale
I have a heart now
Yawns New single Yume wo nakuyuno yozora niYOONS New single "Yume wo nakuenai yozora ni (I can't even draw a dream in the night sky)
Now on sale
Limited Moment
Burn with all your life
It is I who create me
All people
Who do you love more?
Common sense says this way
Tell me your tricks
Lovable youma line
I'll see you later, maquila diane.
I'm sorry, I'm having an emotional shift
New Album Big Love
Now on sale
Halo! Sta.
Next, I would like to ask Shiori Nishida a question
Yes, I will answer!
Shiori Nishida loves to take a nap!
Tell me about a nap you took recently that felt super good.
I woke up just in time.
What is today's fashion?
Denim with flower embroidery.
Five years after winning the Character Award in the Halo Pro trainees' ability assessment test, please describe Shiori Ishida's character in a few words.
Serious
What is your make-up for live performances and what has changed between now and the past?
Eyelashes
If you could only do Hello Project in the past, which group and which tour would you like to see live?
Berryz KOBO's Weekly Berryz Times
Oh, thank you very much.
What do you think are the highlights of the show?
The highlight is that the concept of the live is very clear.
I recently borrowed a dvd from the company and watched it at home.
I borrowed the dvd from the company and watched it at home.
I borrowed the dvd from my office recently and watched it at home, and I really enjoyed it.
I'm sure there are many things that I'd like to buy again, so I thought I'd like to participate in the show.
I'm not very good at it, so I studied a little bit.
I was asked what kind of girl I am, and the first thing I thought of was "serious", so I think I am serious
I'm serious and I'm very professional and I think I'm doing my job.
I'm going to bring it to you later.
I'm Masashi Natsuyaki and this is Kuki Ebata from Juice, and I'll be doing my best again this week. Fluffy pancakes!
How do you like pancakes? Do you like them?
I love them so much!
I love them! I love it!
I like the mixture, too.
Let's get to baking!
Yes!
Let's hope the pancakes are fluffy!
That's important!
First of all, please cook the pancakes slowly over low heat.
Cook it slowly so that it almost disappears.
Brush the pancakes with more oil.
This time, put these rings around the pancakes on a cookie sheet.
Is this to prevent burning?
No, it's not anti-browning. It's more of a sticking prevention.
Okay, so you're going to put about three-quarters of the dough here.
Is that okay?
I think it's fine.
Now, let's put a little lid on this.
They're similar to macarons.
Macarons are similar to meringue.
Macarons are also difficult.
They are crispy, right?
It's good if you can keep them in a fluffy state,
But for macarons, I need to know if I can do it right, like pied.
Pied!
The fluffy part around the macarons.
Is that pied?
That's called pied.
They become fluffy when they are baked.
But sometimes I can't get it right.
It's very difficult.
It's not a hobby.
I don't usually make macarons.
I can't make them.
I can't even think of making them.
They look too difficult.
I think it's the most difficult.
It's better to put a little bit of water here and there to tie it better.
Do you want to do it now? Maybe we could put a little bit in.
It's a little bit open.
Nineteen minutes.19 minutes.
Coming in.
Yes, I'll close it.
Something is cooking meat.
That's for sure.
The sound is gone.
It's gone.
Open it slowly.
Steam might come out. This, you know, might burn you a little bit.
I don't know.
Wow! It's inflated?
It's bulging.
How is it? Can you open it and turn it over now?
I think so.
Ta-da!
Good job!
That's great!
It looks great, doesn't it?
It's going great so far.
It's going to work.
Ready?
Please.
Oh!
Wow!
Oh, it's so beautiful!
And here it is again.
Here, they're stuck together now, so...
Two more.
Wow! It's not done yet.
You're the best, teacher!
They turned out really evenly.
Yes, the color was really beautiful.
I'll take care of it.
Frying pan.
Close.
Close the pan.
Because of the thickness, it's taking longer to cook inside.
That's the fate of fluffiness.
It's our destiny.
What do you think?
I'd better take a look.
Check it out.
How does it smell? Is it okay?
Do you smell the burnt smell? Maybe I should ask you, check it out. How do I smell? It smells really good.
Do you smell the burn?
I'm gonna ask you something.
Let me ask you something.
It's okay, right?
It'll come off, it'll come off, it'll come off.
Here's Miyahizu's point.
Check if the inside is burned with a toothpick.
Please do.
Please check.
You know what I'm talking about.
You've done it before?
Let it go all the way down the middle.
It's a little bit too thin.
Yes, I'll do it.
I'm going. Please do.
Excellent.
Thank goodness. I'm so relieved that the pancake batter is safely cooked.
It looks delicious.
Now let's get to the toppings.
Let's start cutting the fruit.
The knife seems to work reasonably well.
You can be pretty bold.
Hard.
Yes, I hit a bump.
Turn it.
You don't have to put too much force.
When it's all the way there,
Hold it down,
Is the core removed?
Yes, it is.
It's done.
Good.
Be careful.
Yes.
Yes, good.
Drop it here, and then plop it straight down.Drop this here, and then straight and trot.
Yes.
It's done.
Then cut it in half,
Yes.
Shall we slice it?
A little thicker is fine.
Yes.
It's done.
Now, let's slice the strawberries.
Let's start from the tip.
You can stand it up a little more.
A little more.
In front of you.
That's it.
Last.
There you go.
Let's start on the whipped cream.
Yes, sir.
The usual one.
The usual.
I'll mix it.
Yes, please.
I'll put some ice on the bottom now.
I see.
It gets warm while it's spinning.
The fat tends to stick together.
Keep it as cool as possible.
That's right.
Yes, sir.
Okay. Thank you very much.
What do you think, Roddy?
Stop for a second.
Is it ringing a bell?
It'll stand up. That's good.
Finished.
That's great.
Here.
Ah, yes.
You're getting used to it.
Now, let's get to it.
Here are the toppings.
Do whatever you like.
You can use it all up.
Are you sure?
Then, let's go.
Please do it.
First, put a little bit of this here.
Great, great. Plenty.
What do you think I should do? What do you think I should do?
I'm just trying to get an idea of how I want to put the fruit on top.
Around here.
I'm getting my bearings.
It's a cake shop.
But it's so extravagant.
It's too extravagant!
I can just drop it off quickly and easily.
No, I just don't think about it.
It's hard to get the balance right.
Maybe I'm not very good at serving it, but...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's done!
Fluffy pancakes are ready!
What do you think, Shibata?
Well, it's quite a fluffy pancake, plus..,
plus dynamic cream and fruits,
I made a pancake that looks like a large cake,
They are absolutely delicious,
I did my best to make it, so please try it as soon as possible.
Please try it and eat it with these strawberries on top.
Put these strawberries on it and eat it.
It's so fluffy. The fluffiness, the sweetness of the cream and pancake, and the tartness of the strawberries make it so delicious.
It's delicious.
It was good. What do you think? Was it a success?
It was a great success.
I'm glad.
I'm so happy.
But you know, Ibarachan and her teacher had talked a lot about how she usually cooks,But Ibarachan and her teacher had talked a lot about how she cooks on a regular basis,
This was Ibarachan's first time to appear in Hello Kitchen,
How did you like it? How was your first time?
Yes, it was. I usually cook and make sweets,
I was a little nervous, but it was the first time for me to make something in front of the camera,
I was a little nervous,
But Natsuyaki-san and the teacher were very kind and it was a lot of fun.
It was really good. I was really happy.
It was the first time for me to talk to them, so I was really happy.
Thank you very much.
That was Hello Kitchen.
Well, it looked delicious.
It looked like a very cute one-pack, though.
I'm so nervous about that Hello Kitchen.
It's not about cooking anymore, is it? I felt a little bit nervous because Natsuyaki-san, a senior chef, was there.
I felt like I'm going to be so nervous because Natsuyaki-san, the senior chef, is there, but I wanted to eat pancakes, so I made some at home.
I wanted to have pancakes at home, but I burnt them so badly, but you know, pancakes require a little more skill than you think.
So after watching this video, I thought I'd like to learn a little bit more.
When it comes to making sweets...
I'm the kind of person who does things on the spur of the moment.
But I don't know... I'm too impulsive.
When I haven't prepared something yet, but it's already here...
I summon my mother, who's like a mother, to help me out, but in the end, I'm not sure if it's going to take shape.
But in the end, I think it's going to take shape.
I think we both want to do our best in cooking, making sweets, and making sweets.
I'm going to do my best in cooking and making sweets. Sta.
We are Shiori Nishida from BEYOOOOONDS Subway and Miyo Hirai from BEYOOOOONDS Seasonings. Stay!
Now we are in the second half of the BEYOOOOONDS concert tour NEOBIO, which started in March. This tour is called NEOBIO, and we are trying our best to show you a new BEYOOOOONDS, but what kind of tour is it?
Well, we didn't put a lot of emphasis on each member's specialties, but this time you will be able to enjoy them as well.
You've got it.
Yes! Of course, we put a lot of thought into the singing voices and the composition of the songs, so I think you will enjoy it.
I'm surprised that it's already the second half of the season.
I'm sure you'll enjoy it, but I'm surprised that it's already the second half of the season.
I'm sure you will be even more enthusiastic about this second show at the Nippon Budokan, but was there anything memorable about the first show?
One of the most memorable moments was when BEYOOOOONDS came out for encore and we were all able to wear the sparkling fluffy skirt costumes that we had dreamed of wearing together.
I've been allowed to wear many outfits in the past,
But until now, we had been allowed to wear a lot of costumes, but most of them were colorful and chaotic, and the members wore them separately,
But we were all allowed to wear super cute costumes with fluffy skirts,
I was really happy about that, and it left a lasting impression on me.
Yes, at this point we are gradually getting to know what the Nippon Budokan concert will be like,
We are sure that everyone will really enjoy the concert, so let's meet at the Nippon Budokan! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
I want to be! I can't! I want to try!
Fresh dreams this and that!
The sparkle is always fresh
Believe and you'll be fine!
Sour and sweet are all multiplied together in today's world
Sweet and sour are multiplied together in the modern age
One plus one
The new Ollie Wang
Surprisingly OK!
Feelings Ideas
I've got tomorrow
full of dreams
so many things to choose from
so many choices, so many choices, so many choices, so many choices, so many choices, so many choices, so many choices, so many choices, so many choices
Seven, twelve, one, POPPIN
But first, bread
Aim at me, I'm a wanderer
I want to be a tea receiver
I've got so many, I've got so many, I've got so many, I've got so many
I'll just go for it and beat it!
I'm not done yet, I'm just getting started
Let's make it all come true
More Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey, Hey! No! Khakis?
Mistake!
So days?
No!
Long, isn't it?
Shall I ask? The litter is lost.
It's so melty, it's so melty
I'm so full of dreams, I'm so full of dreams
Drizzle, drizzle, drizzle, drizzle, drizzle...
Don't you ever talk about yourself?
I've got a plan, but I've got a great future
If you're brave enough to stand up for yourself
It's my time
Because, in fact...
Night green, night green, night green, night green
I can't hide my current crush
See, jia jia jia jia jia!Look, jia jia jia jia jia!
You killed my friend!
Aah!
I surprised him!
That's so cool!
Green, green, green.
Green, green, green
I want to be honest.
I knew it! I knew it!
Chikutara-sasa!
I can do anything I want
I can do anything!
The source of a dream as sweet as a peach... a strawberry... a single layer of life.
I did it just once!
My fingers are done!
What do you want to do?
It's no use!
Drink your tea!
Seranda.
Arum.
Pollen.
You said you'd stay.
Go Go, hang in there.
I can handle you.
Cheer up only
No muscat introductions today.
My journey may be long, but I won't give up a single word
Ah, here I go!
I want to hear your dreams
I have many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many
I can't choose just one, they're all documented
jaga kinke, pappapapon, but first, bread!
Seino, ewwa, kushikake
Ocha-tea-tea
every second, every second, every second, every second
I'll never be able to choose, I'll take them all!
I'm not done yet, I'm just getting started
Let's make what we want come true... more
Let's do our best tomorrow!
This message is brought to you by Shori Nishida of BEYOOOOONDS Subway
BEYOOOOONDS Seasonings' Hirai Miyo presents Halo! Stay!
It's time to say goodbye!
Here's an announcement!
BEYOOOOONDS concert tour on May 15
NeoBio at Budokan will be held on May 15!
This will be the second time for us to perform at the Nippon Budokan,
The 12 of us will join forces and do our best, so please give us your support.
And we are now holding our spring tour, Beyond Concert Tour Neovio.
The next concert will be in Yamaguchi on May 20.
We will all enjoy ourselves as much as we can and bring you the best entertainment show.
We will definitely thrill you, so please look forward to it.
And now the fourth single,
Seek Me, Fate's Traveller, on the night sky where you can't even draw a dream.
If you haven't seen the music videos yet, please check them out,
If you haven't seen them yet, please take a look!
Haloste is a channel where the members of Hello Project appear on the show.
New videos are uploaded every Wednesday.
Please subscribe to our channel!
This time, I'm joined by BEYOOOOONDS' Chica Tetsu Shiori Nishida and
and Miyo Hirai from BEYOOOOONDS Seasonings.
Bye bye you!